The British government has called for more men to consider a career in nursing.
Figures show the number of male nurses has fallen in the last three years.
Now the number of working in the nursing sector has reached a seven -year low.
Numbers of male nurses increased between 2011 and 2014 and reached
Now the number of men working in the nursing sector has reached a seven -year low.
Numbers of male nurses increased between 2011 and 2014 and reached the same of in
the nursing sector as in
Numbers of male nurses increased between 2011 and 2014 and reached a peak of 7,168.
This figure has dropped to only 6,924 in 2017.
The UK Health Secretary said, This is clearly a cultural problem, and probably one
that exists in many parts of the world.
This figure has dropped to only 6,924 in 2017.
The UK Health Secretary said, This is clearly a cultural problem, and probably one
that exists in many parts of the world.
This figure has dropped to only 6,924 in 2017.
The UK Health Secretary said, is clearly a cultural problem, and probably one that
exists in many parts of the world.
But we can make efforts to change that now.
We want to persuade males to think about career options of going into nursing.
But we